♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good
old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
We now return to Rational Geographic.
Upon realizing a trip to Africa
would be smelly and gross,
our crew decided to stay in the office.
Aah! Mom, Dad! A bat, a bat!
Oh, my God, there's a bat in the house.
Okay, all-all right,
everybody just calm down,
it might just be Grandpa Munster.
Somebody set him up for a funny joke.
Hey, Grandpa,
how did you sleep last night?
Yeah, see, if it was
him, he would have said,
"Like I do every night: upside down."
Okay. But Peter,
we can't have a bat
flying around the house.
We got to do something.
Don't worry, Lois. I'll get rid of it.
It'll be a piece of cake.
Just like my penis enhancement.
I want it to hang down to my knees.
They moved up my knees.
Everybody, I've come up with the
perfect plan to catch the bat.
I bought this remote-
controlled toy helicopter,
to which I have attached this handgun.
And I tell you, this thing
is not easy to fly.
- Peter, that doesn't seem very...
- Here goes.
Now, I don't have anything
to control the trigger with,
so I put it on a timer.
But I don't remember
how long I set it...
Aah! We're all gonna die!
Okay, so, now the bat has a
gun, and the knives I gave him.
What? Why would you give him knives?
I didn't think it would matter.
I was counting on this
helicopter thing working.
Peter? Wh-where are you?
What's going on?
In order to understand the bat,
we must first understand the vampire.
So I watched Interview With the Vampire.
Cast your gaze upon...
Lestat.
Peter, you're not a vampire.
Oh? Then why am I clad in velvet pants
tucked into soft leather boots?
And why does my shirt billow so
in the wind of that rotating fan?
Peter, what's really going on?
I'm just tryin' to reinvent my look.
A guy at work said I dress like crap.
Well, you show 'em tomorrow, Peter.
How'd it go?
I was sent home early and
labeled a distraction.
They're having a meeting
about me tomorrow.
Wha... Wh-What's wrong?
Ar-Are we taking a
terrible 7:00 a.m. flight?
No no. I realized to catch a bat,
I need to live like a bat.
So I got to be up at night.
It's a nocturnal mission, Lois.
Okay, but what are you gonna do?
Well, as everyone knows,
bats watch a ton of
Cinemax softcore porn,
so that seems like the place to start.
A-ha!
Welcome back to CNBC's Moneyline.
Oh come on, man, nobody's buyin' that.
You expect me to believe you own stocks?
Bat Industries was up two
dollars a share today
in heavy trading.
Huh.
Get back here! Damn it!
Aah!
I got you now, Bat Damon.
I named you Bat Damon.
Aw, now I want you to live.
Aah! Aah! What is it?
- Aah!
- Ow!
You can beat me, but I am who I am!
Peter, what the hell did
you do to Stewie's hand?
It could be broken.
I didn't mean to. It's just,
sometimes I don't think before I act.
Oh, hey, high-five.
Hey, did you just high-five that sign?
Yeah.
You think differently.
Get in.
His name was Derek.
But he went by the Prophet
when times were good,
or the Law Giver when times were bad.
I moved onto his prayer
farm with 45 other members
of the Salvation Star Boys,
who died in a mass suicide.
But not me. 'Cause I
don't like root beer.
And I only drink what I like.
After it was all over, I
called Lois to pick me up.
She was mad.
But she's what Derek calls
an Oppressing Doubter.
May the light of Derek's
Invincible Diamond
shine through you.
Oh, thank you so much for
coming in early, Dr. Hartman.
Oh, no problem.
- Hell, I used to work here.
- What?
Good news. Stewie's hand looks fine.
Oh, hey, high-five.
Huh. As long as you're here,
I see Stewie hasn't had
his vaccinations yet.
Should we take care of that?
Well, I suppose so.
Oh, but first, I'm required to
have you read this pamphlet
about the risks of vaccinations.
God, you are aging so rapidly.
"Possible side effects:
fever, severe allergic reaction,
muscle and joint pain?"
Wait, and this can't be right:
they actually put some of
the disease in the shot?
Hey, man, how many
questions your lady ask?
Uh, like, a million?
But I don't remember
having to read any of this
when Chris and Meg had
their vaccinations.
Well, that was before
Internet chat rooms
made everybody an expert.
It's a better world now.
I-I don't know about this, Dr. Hartman.
We might need a little bit
of time to think this over.
Yeah, 'cause we don't want
to make a big mistake.
Like when I peed next to the chatty guy.
Hey, man, we should get out of here,
the building's on fire.
Hey, pal, not now, I'm busy.
Anyway, I'll tell you
what's on fire, my urethra.
That's the last time I
go to a water park,
I'll tell you that much.
Well, that's not completely true,
'cause I have a Groupon,
and I'd hate to waste it.
Plus, the truth is, the kids...
Oh, my God...
I was the chatty guy.
Hey, you guys, is that my laptop?
Yeah, sorry, we were
looking something up.
We were going to get Stewie vaccinated,
but now, after our research,
we're definitely not.
Ah, no, Lois, don't tell me
you fell for all that anti-vaxxer crap.
It's not crap, Brian.
There's a lot of evidence
to suggest there's a link
between vaccinations and autism.
Lois, all that so-called
evidence has been debunked.
Listen to some of these ingredients:
"mercury, thimerosal,
aluminum, formaldehyde."
Lois, deciding not to vaccinate Stewie
is something that affects all of us.
The only reason they work
is that if a critical mass
of society gets immunized,
then the diseases won't spread.
Look, Brian, I was skeptical, too,
but then I did some research
and I found some very interesting things
from the leader of the
anti-vaccination movement,
Jenny McCarthy.
See? Proof.
Hard to argue with that.
And look at this one.
Glasses.
Case closed.
I can't believe you guys.
Don't you realize you're contributing
to a potential public health disaster
by not vaccinating your child?
That's exactly the point... My child.
He's my child,
and nothing matters more
than his well-being.
Oh, God, this is going to
be a Lois story, isn't it?
Game of Thrones is on, just a reminder.
Yeah, we made this mistake before.
We got the other kids vaccinated,
but Meg still got chicken pox.
Dad, this is acne.
Girl, you nasty.
You realize the vast majority
of people think you're wrong.
Well, maybe that's the problem.
We just got to change their minds.
We're gettin' this town
to change its mind
about vaccinations.
Yeah. I'm with you.
Just as soon as I finish
gettin' the word out
about the one thing more important.
The brothers who made The
Matrix are ladies now!
They're ladies!
Just one of 'em?
That's the thing... It's both of 'em!
What are the chances?
What are the chances?!
The brothers who made The
Matrix are ladies now!
All right, come on, Peter,
I've got all the stuff for
our anti-vaccination rally.
I don't believe this.
It's bad enough you guys
aren't vaccinating Stewie.
Now you're trying to
convince other people
to make the same reckless choice?
I'm also gonna pet a bunch
of dogs without asking.
Don't do that. We don't like that.
Then I'm gonna try and
look at their teeth.
Brian, all we want is for
parents to have the choice.
Because parents know what's
best for their kids.
I hear Sansa finally
shows boob in this one.
You do realize they're
putting your life in danger
by not getting you immunized.
You could get measles, mumps,
rubella, whooping cough...
Oh, my God, are you serious?
Very serious. Even the tiniest germ
could make you very ill and,
left untreated, kill you.
Really?
I'd expect this kind of thing
from the fat man, but not Lois.
Although she did act like a nutcase
that time she went shopping
right before Thanksgiving.
Ready for Turkey Day?
Clever.
Don't eat too much turkey tomorrow.
Oh, I won't.
Now, if only the meal
would cook itself, huh?
Parents of Quahog
and weekend dads playing
three minutes of catch,
do you know that the number
of childhood vaccines
has tripled in the last generation?
And why is that?
Because heartless corporations
make billions of dollars
by foisting garbage and
poison upon our children.
We demand that these vaccines
be tested by independent researchers,
not by the companies who make them.
Excuse me, are you the
lady selling the bullhorn?
What? No.
I'm over here.
Damn it.
This doesn't seem to be working.
Well, obviously, Lois.
You can't just go to a park
and list a bunch of boring facts.
You got to spice things up.
Like I did when I was a lounge singer
with uneven lyric density.
This is a song I wrote for
my beautiful girlfriend.
Her name is...
♪ Kim ♪
♪ I don't understand why your father ♪
♪ Has such problems with us ♪
♪ Kim ♪
♪ Mostly I think it's because ♪
♪ I don't make my car payments on time ♪
♪ But also because I was
dating someone else ♪
♪ At the same time as ♪
♪ Kim ♪
Two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight,
nine, ten, eleven.
♪ Kim ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ But mostly I love that you let
me eat crackers in the bed ♪
♪ Kim! ♪
Thank you!
Eh, that's enough of that.
What the hell?
Peter, is that you on TV right now?
Oh yeah, that's my anti-vaccination PSA.
Hi, I'm a medical guy,
and I'm here to give you
the facts about vaccs.
Fact... Vaccinations cause autism,
paralysis, and even...
death, death, death, death,
death, death, death,
death, death, death.
Fact: "vaccinate" rhymes
with "masturbate."
Would you let a doctor
do that to your kid?
Fact: I still think Michelle
Williams is Carey Mulligan.
Fact!
Medical delivery for
badass karate doctor.
Ah yes, those must be
the bones and skulls.
I see no boob bones,
the victim was a man.
Wow.
♪ Oh, yeah! ♪
Say "no" to vaccines.
Paid for with Meg's college fund.
What the hell is all this?
I'm trying to protect myself
from all those diseases
I'm not vaccinated against.
Speaking of which, do you
have any idea the germs
you routinely track into this house?
From now on I'm going to ask
that you wear these shoes
while indoors.
Where'd you get those?
Put 'em on and lick your lips!
Stewie, you might be
taking this too far.
Proper hygiene depends
on everyone, Brian.
For instance, I've already
saran-wrapped Chris.
I'm a gas station sandwich!
We interrupt this program
with breaking news.
Childhood vaccination rates
in Quahog have dropped
to an all-time low, fueled
by a recent media campaign
led by local meddler, Peter Griffin,
shown here in the basket
of Henry Thomas' bicycle.
That can't be real, right?
Oh, I knew one of these
had to be my house.
Damn it, Peter, thanks to you,
nobody in this town is
vaccinating their kids anymore!
Do you even realize the
harm you've caused?
Harm? What are you talking about?
I'm making the world a better place.
Like when I was the Instagram police.
Sorry, lady, got to crop the chotch.
I... will take this.
And cutaway complete.
Man, there is a lot of bad
art in these hallways.
All right, Stewie, see you after school.
Wait a minute, where are
all the other kids?
Haven't you heard?
There's been an outbreak of measles.
It's all because everyone
stopped vaccinating their kids.
Oh, my God!
And it's not just our school.
Kids all over town are getting sick.
Attention! Attention!
What the hell?
People of Quahog,
your town is under quarantine.
Until further notice, no one
may enter or leave the city.
Oh, that's the guy who bought
the bullhorn at the park.
Oh, this is awful.
It's all our fault!
And look, Joe's arguing
with a state policeman
over jurisdiction.
Thanks, Swanson, we'll
take it from here.
It's a state matter now.
No way, this is my town.
Thanks, guys, the feds
will take it from here.
Oh, no, this is my state.
Hi, I'm a crossing guard who can walk,
so I have jurisdiction over all of you.
Must be serious.
They brought in the big guns.
You happy now, Lois?
Because of you, there's
a measles epidemic,
and the whole town is quarantined.
Speak for yourself, Brian.
I, for one, am enjoying
the indoor family time.
Who's up for another game
of hot-breath telephone?
We're all gonna die!
Chris, you're supposed to whisper
that to the next person.
Peter, Brian's right!
We were wrong about everything!
We've got to get to the hospital
and get Stewie vaccinated!
Eh, it might be a little
too late for that.
I kind of destroyed all
the vaccines in town.
All right, what else did
I have to do today?
Ah, yes, overdose in my apartment.
I better get home.
You destroyed all the vaccines?
Yeah, but it's fine. There's
nothing to worry about.
Is anyone else feeling feverish, achy,
and acutely sensitive to light?
Oh, my God, Peter.
Y-you've got measles!
Now, hold on, hold on,
before we all freak out,
it might just be full-body herpes.
Wait, you guys, Dad might
not have been vaccinated.
Didn't Grandma say he
was born in Mexico?
Nobody remembers that, Meg.
We got to keep you away from Stewie.
You'll get him sick.
Oh, my little guy's gonna be fine.
All he needs is a good,
old-fashioned game
of hot-breath telephone.
Measles.
I've got to get out of this house,
or I'll be in worse shape
than John Goodman!
I've got your EKG here.
How does it look?
Well, it spells out "Pancakes."
Oh, okay, so same as last time.
I'm recommending you go on
a strict diet immediately.
Nope.
Horses that make it
look like I can walk,
take me to Hollywood!
All right, I'm almost done packing.
I've got it down to
four bags and a hatbox.
I'm gonna need some help, Rupert.
Rupert?
Ew, that's the tushie thermometer.
Dear God, you're burning up!
I have to get out of here!
I'm sorry, Rupert.
But the situation here
has become unbearable.
Like talking to someone
with adult braces.
So, yeah, last weekend,
Sheila and I took the kids
up to the lake, it was great.
We had great weather,
fired up the barbecue,
Sheila's parents came up
towards the end of the week...
When are you gonna get those off?
Meg, you must carry on my legacy.
Promise me you'll crop the chotches.
Crop them, Meg!
Crop them all!
Peter, Stewie's gone!
I've looked everywhere!
Oh, Lois, I feel a little better.
I think I could keep down deviled eggs.
Lois, what's wrong?
I can't find Stewie.
He must've gotten out of the house.
God knows how far he's gone.
Well, look, there's a
Family Circus dotted path.
It'll lead us right to him.
Ah, it's just Billy.
He died of measles.
And here comes Marmaduke
to lick up the vomit.
Lucky.
If I can just escape this quarantine
and make it to the next town,
I'll be able to get that vaccine I need.
Stewie! I'm you from the future!
You've got to get the hell out
of town before you get sick!
Yeah, I know. That's what I'm doing.
Okay, I'm really here because
I know you have glue.
Give me the glue.
Stewie, listen to me,
never, ever do this great thing I love.
There's the bridge out of town!
So we're all there at the Clam,
just kind of making music together,
and then Peter, of
course, had to join in
and clap his hands, and I said,
"Eh, that's enough of that."
Yeah, I kind of run the group.
I'll just have to go around them.
Good Lord.
I hope my shoe doesn't
fall to make me realize
how far the drop is.
Oh, my orthotic was in there.
Stewie?
Where are you?
Lois, what's going on?
That's one of my sidekicks' wives.
He says he's in charge of
the group, is that true?
No, not in the slightest, but,
Joe, Stewie's gone missing.
We can't find him anywhere.
Lois, look!
I don't know if he can
hold on much longer.
We got to get him down.
Stewie, hang on!
Mommy's coming!
Oh, no, upside-down train!
- Stewie!
- Oh, no!
Sean Penn?
That's right, two-time
Oscar winner Sean Penn.
What are you doing here?
I'm bringing vaccines into
your quarantined town.
Any time there's a public health
crisis in a third-world land,
I'm there.
Third world? This is Rhode Island.
Oh, really?
Have you seen some of the
delis on Federal Hill?
Oh-ho-ho! Rhode Island slam!
Ho-ho! I like you, Sean Penn.
Oh, my God, you saved my baby!
Thank you so mu... Oh.
Sean Penn.
You're the one who
played that homosexual.
Yeah.
All right, well, I'll take my son now.
I've brought enough vaccines
for your whole town.
I hope you've realized
that vaccinations are not
a freedom of choice issue,
they're a public health issue.
Thanks to them, countless
serious diseases, mumps, polio,
smallpox, and rubella, have
been all but eradicated.
Like clean water and functional schools,
vaccinations are a human right.
Great, just what I needed, a
lecture from liberal Hollywood.
This whole thing has been a
Well, it's a relief that
everyone's been vaccinated,
and the quarantine has been lifted.
Well, I'm just happy
that Stewie is healthy,
and only 150 people died, but
not anyone we knew personally.
Yeah, I know I sure learned something.
Hey, do you like apples?
Yeah.
Well, I got her number.
How do you like them apples?
Oh, Bat Damon!
You got the best of me again!
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru